garminasus.com 2018-12-09

# Privacy Policy | Garmin

Our goal is to make sure you know how we collect, use, share and store your personal data when you create a Garmin account, interact with our customer support specialists and visit [Garmin.com](https://www.garmin.com/ "Garmin.com") or other Garmin websites and apps covered by this privacy policy.

## What data does Garmin collect?

We ask for personal data — such as your name, email address, location and other information — so you can sign in to your accounts, receive personalized support, receive important safety information about your devices and get the most out of our products. 

Learn More

### When You Make an Account

Garmin stores information such as your name, email address and passwords so you can log in, and it helps us verify your account if you call customer support. 

### When You Use Social Media

If you sign in to your Garmin account using social media, we ask to access certain information to help create the account. We only store your email address for signing in later. 

### When You Buy Products

When you buy products from Garmin, we ask for information such as your name, address and phone number so we can get your order processed and shipped to you.

### When You Sync Products

When you sync your device, we collect data such as your IP address, sync time and date and battery level to help identify and resolve errors or syncing issues and to provide better customer support.

### When You Contact Garmin

We know you want to stay off the grid, but we may collect things such as your contact and device information during support calls to ensure that you get the help you need. 

### When You Use Location Features

Sometimes we need to collect your device’s location. That makes it a lot easier to tell you about things such as weather in your area, nearby traffic and even movie prices near you. 

### When You Use Auto Navigation

With your consent, Garmin collects information that includes location, direction and speed to help with features such as parking and traffic. 

## Why does Garmin ask for your personal data?

From providing product support to offering clear directions to your destination, any information we ask you for is used to improve your experience with Garmin.

Learn More

### To Keep You Informed

When we have something important to tell you about your products, apps and account — such as vital safety information, app updates, new products or deals and updates to our privacy policy — we use collected contact information to reach you.

### To Improve Our Sites

When you visit our sites, we collect information — such as your IP address, location, times that you visit and more — to let us know how people navigate our site and how we can improve it. 

### To Give You Information You Might Actually Find Interesting

We use things such as cookies, pixel tags and similar tools to help us provide better, more relevant content on our sites. So if you and everyone else are coming to Garmin.com for awesome fitness devices, we’ll know to keep making them. 

We also use these tools to see how effective our ads are and to identify any problems that we need to fix. All in all, we just want to give you a website worth browsing. 

## Does Garmin sell your personal data?

No! We don’t sell your personal data to anyone. And we only share your personal data with others in specific situations. 

Learn More

### Data Shared Within Garmin 

Garmin is global, which means your personal data may be stored locally or in another country or transferred between Garmin companies. No matter where your information is within Garmin, it is still secured under this privacy policy. 

### Data Shared with Service Providers 

We share personal data with third parties who provide services — such as fulfilling orders and sending emails to customers — for us. 

### Data Shared for Legal Reasons

Garmin will share your personal data when required to by law enforcement and in other legal matters. 

### Data Shared with Content and Feature Providers

With your consent, we share information collected from your auto navigation device — such as location, direction and speed — with third parties that provide content and features such as traffic and parking information. 

## How can you share your personal data?

Your personal data belongs to you, and you control what you share and whom you share it with. 

Learn More

### LiveTrack

You can share a link to your device’s real-time location with your friends and family so they can follow along on your journey. 

### Promotions

We post contests and sweepstakes so you can win stuff. If you enter a contest or sweepstakes, we need to use the information you give us to make sure you get that stuff if you win.

## How can I request to view, update, delete or transfer my data?

Visit [Account Management Center ](https://www.garmin.com/account) to make your request. Learn more about your rights in the Garmin.com privacy policy.
